formidablepro.com 2018-12-19

# Privacy Policy - Formidable Forms

Strategy11, LLC a Delaware limited liability company (“Strategy11”), owns and operates several websites including FormidableForms.com. We are committed to the privacy and security of our visitors’ information. The following is a statement of our privacy practices:

**Information Collected**

  * Your personal information is not required to visit FormidableForms.com
  * Any personal information collected is knowingly provided by you and only when requested/required. This includes information collected during account registration for interactive participation on FormidableForms.com, help desk ticket creation, comments anywhere on our site, and during the ordering process.

**Comments**

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection. An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment. This site uses Akismet to reduce spam. [Learn how your comment data is processed](https://automattic.com/privacy-notice/).

**Traffic Data**

  * Your IP address is a numeric address assigned to your computer, assigned by your Internet service provider. We automatically collect your IP address as traffic data so that we can send information back to you when requested. This is not used to identify your personal information.
  * Referrers are references to the web address you linked from and is automatically passed along by your web browser. We collect referrers your browser sends as part of traffic data. This is not attached to personally identifiable information.
  * System information such as your operating system/platform, and the type of web browser you use. This is not attached to personally identifiable information.

**Account Information**

  * Your information is maintained on a secure web server in what we believe to be a well protected environment.
  * Strategy11 only shares personal information to billing companies for completing transactions and for no other purpose. No other information is shared with any other third-party company for any purpose, under any circumstance.
  * Strategy11 makes every effort to preserve your privacy, personal information may be disclosed when required by law where we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or legal process.

**Cookies**

FormidableForms.com relies on “cookie” technology to allow you to re-access your registered account profile during a web session. This mechanism is employed solely for your convenience and for no other purpose.

**Links**

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, Strategy11, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our visitors to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Security**

This web site takes every precaution to protect our visitor’s information. When visitors submit sensitive information via the web site, their information is protected both online and off-line. We do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our customers’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are in a secure environment, in a locked facility. If visitors have any questions about the security on FormidableForms.com, feel free to contact Customer Service.

**Correcting, Updating, Deleting & Deactivating Personal Information**

If a visitor’s personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a visitor no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate personally identifiable information. This can usually be done at the ‘Your Account’ page or by contacting our Customer Service.

**Ads**

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Strategy11 and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Business Transfers**

If Strategy11, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Strategy11 goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Strategy11 may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

**Privacy Policy Changes**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Strategy11 may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Strategy11’s sole discretion. Strategy11 encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

**Contact Information**

If visitors have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: [Customer Service Form](https://formidableforms.com/new-topic/) 

Phone: (801) 610-9460 Strategy11, LLC  12180 S 300 E #785 Draper, UT 84020
